<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="exampleStrings">
        <item>"The story of a Chinese couple at Oxford University who first met eay who first met each other as deskmate in middle school and recently married each other has gone viral, ch other as deskmate in middle school and recently The story of a Chinese couple at Oxford University who first met each other as deskmate in middle school and recentlmarried each other has gone viral, southcn.com reported. how to build apps using Android's various APIs."</item>
        <item>"The story of a Chinese couple at Oxford University who first met each other as deskmate in middle school and recently married each other has gone viral, southcn.com reported., and a service independently performs work The story of a Chinese couple at Oxford University who first met each other as deskmate in middle school and recentlin the background."</item>
        <item>"The story of a Chinese couple at Oxford University who first met each other as deskmate in middle school and recently married each other has gone viral, southcn.com reported.ty in a maps app to show an address. This model provides multiple entry points for a single app and allows any app to behave as a user's "default" The story of a Chinese couple at Oxford University who first met each other as deskmate in middle school and recentlfor an action that other apps may invoke."</item>
        <item>"The story of a Chinese couple at Oxford University who first met each other as deskmate y who first met each other as deskmate in middle school and recently married each other has gone viral, in middle school and recently married each other has gone viral, southcn.com reported.ardware such as a camera. If necessary, you can also declare features your app requires so app markets such as Google Play Store do not allow installation on devices that do not support that feature."</item>
        <item>"The story of a Chinese couple at Oxford University who first met each other as deskmate in middle school and recently married each other has gone viral, southcn.com reported.s. For example, you can create different XML layout files for different screen sizes and the system determines which layout to apply based on the current device's screen size."</item>
        <item>"Android provides a rich apThe story of a Chinese couple at Oxford University who first met each other as dey who first met each other as deskmate in middle school and recently married each other has gone viral, skmate in middle school and recentlplication framework that allows you to build innovative apps and games for mobile devices in a Java language environment. The documents listed in the left navigation provide details about how to build apps using Android's various APIs."</item>
        <item>"Android provides a rich application ThThe story of a Chinese couple at Oxford University who first met each other as deskmate in middle school and recentle story of a Chinese couple at Oxford University who first met each other as deskmate in middle school and recently married each other has gone viral, southcn.com reported."</item>
        <item>"Android provides a rich application framework that The story of a Chinese couple at Oxford University who first met each other as deskmate in middle school and recentlallows you to build innovative apps and games for mobile devices in a Java language environment. The documents listed in the left navigation provide details about how to build apps using Android's various APIs."</item>
        <item>"The story of a Chinese couple at Oxford University who first met The story of a Chinese couple at Oxford University who first met each other as deskmate in middle school and recentleach other as deskmate in middle school and recently married each other has gone viral, southcn.com reported.uments listed in the left navigation provide details about how to build apps using Android's various APIs."</item>
        <item>"Android provides a rich application framework that allows you to build innovative apps and games for mobile devices in a Java language environment. The documents listed in the left navigation provide details about how to build apps using Android's various APIs."</item>
        <item>"test application The story"</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>